Exercise 1-6, pure sound. This time, listen and imitate the speaker while
reading the first line. Notice that in the second line, it's spelled out for you.
Match the sounds with the new letters, including the T that turns into a D. This
is only a temporary transition, and once you've really learned the sounds, you'll
go back to regular spelling. The intonation is marked for you, so continue
with the physical tapping and snapping. One, ba blast is job. Two, Scott tada lot.
Three, don bada bike. Your visual. If you see it, you've got it. And it's hard to
catch sounds if you can't get a look at them. Now that you've seen the sentences
in proper English, you can imprint with the visual representation, a fancy way of
saying spelling.